{
    "subject": "Prince_Karl_Anton_of_Hohenzollern",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Princess_Jos\u00e9phine_Caroline_of_Belgium",
    "human_readable": "Prince Karl Anton of Hohenzollern is married to Princess Jos\u00e9phine Caroline of Belgium.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9705144762992859,
            "question": "Are Princess Jos\u00e9phine Caroline and Prince Karl Anton married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9687818288803101,
            "question": "To whom is Prince Karl Anton of Hohenzollern married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9571145176887512,
            "question": "Who is married to Princess Jos\u00e9phine Caroline of Belgium?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9491576552391052,
            "question": "Is Princess Jos\u00e9phine Caroline of Belgium married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9201668500900269,
            "question": "Who is Prince Karl Anton of Hohenzollern?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7451292872428894,
            "question": "What is the name of Prince Karl Anton's wife?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.721329927444458,
            "question": "Is there a connection between  Prince Karl Anton and Belgium?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6894677877426147,
            "question": "What is the nationality of Princess Jos\u00e9phine Caroline?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44690215587615967,
            "question": "What title does Prince Karl Anton hold?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.39610233902931213,
            "question": "What is the full name of the Belgian princess?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Prince Karl Anton of Hohenzollern is married to Princess Jos\u00e9phine Caroline of Belgium.",
            "html": "yago_26496_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What title does Prince Karl Anton hold?",
            "html": "yago_26496_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the nationality of Princess Jos\u00e9phine Caroline?",
            "html": "yago_26496_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there a connection between  Prince Karl Anton and Belgium?",
            "html": "yago_26496_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26496_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26496_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26496_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26496_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26496_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26496_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26496_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26496_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26496_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26496_61.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Prince Karl Anton of Hohenzollern is married to Princess Jos\u00e9phine Caroline of Belgium.\" Specifically, both 57.txt and 34.txt mention their marriage on 28 May 1894 in Brussels."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}